[{"answer": "0 to 5:00 every day.  They have one daughter", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 7, "question": "", "qSentId": 6},{"answer": "0 and then stays at a friends house until 5:30", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 7, "question": "0 to 5:00 every day.  They have one daughter", "qSentId": 6},{"answer": " Lucy, can you set the table for me", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 11, "question": "0 and then stays at a friends house until 5:30", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Just a minute, mom.  Im watching TV", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 12, "question": " Lucy, can you set the table for me", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Lucy, please turn off the TV and do it now.  I dont want to have to as", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Just a minute, mom.  Im watching TV", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Fine, mom.  Im coming.  Wheres dad", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Lucy, please turn off the TV and do it now.  I dont want to have to as", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " I guess hes still at the gym.  He was supposed to be home by now", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Fine, mom.  Im coming.  Wheres dad", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Oh.  Whats for dinner", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 19, "question": " I guess hes still at the gym.  He was supposed to be home by now", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Macaroni and cheese and broccoli", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Oh.  Whats for dinner", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Not again.  We always have that", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Macaroni and cheese and broccoli", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Lucy, stop complaining.  You should be thankful that we have food to ea", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Not again.  We always have that", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Cant I have something else, mom?  Im sick of mac and cheese", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Lucy, stop complaining.  You should be thankful that we have food to ea", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " No, you cant.  I just got home from work and have spent an hou", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Cant I have something else, mom?  Im sick of mac and cheese", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Fine, I will", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 34, "question": " No, you cant.  I just got home from work and have spent an hou", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Hi, everyone.  Im home", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Fine, I will", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Dad, youre home", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Hi, everyone.  Im home", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Hi, Jim.  Where were you?  You said youd be home 20 minutes ago", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Dad, youre home", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Sorry, hon. The gym was packed.  I had to wait 15 minutes just to get in th", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Hi, Jim.  Where were you?  You said youd be home 20 minutes ago", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Well, dinner is ready.  Lets sit down", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Sorry, hon. The gym was packed.  I had to wait 15 minutes just to get in th", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " So, how was your day at work Marcia", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Well, dinner is ready.  Lets sit down", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Oh, it was pretty bad.  Im stuck working on a project with Dan again", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 44, "question": " So, how was your day at work Marcia", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Did you talk to the boss about it", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Oh, it was pretty bad.  Im stuck working on a project with Dan again", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " No, I dont want to seem like I cant work with other people.  Im jus", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Did you talk to the boss about it", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " It sounds like it.  Why dont you relax tonight after dinner?  Ill do the dishe", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 55, "question": " No, I dont want to seem like I cant work with other people.  Im jus", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " That sounds wonderful.  Thank you, honey", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 59, "question": " It sounds like it.  Why dont you relax tonight after dinner?  Ill do the dishe", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " So, how was your day at school", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 60, "question": " That sounds wonderful.  Thank you, honey", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " It was great daddy.  We learned about wolves", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 61, "question": " So, how was your day at school", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Wolves, huh", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 62, "question": " It was great daddy.  We learned about wolves", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " MmmHmmm.  They live in packs", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Wolves, huh", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Well thats interesting.  Maybe this weekend we could go to the zoo and se", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 64, "question": " MmmHmmm.  They live in packs", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Yeah!  Thatd be awesome", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Well thats interesting.  Maybe this weekend we could go to the zoo and se", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Did you finish all of your homework at Kims house after school", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Yeah!  Thatd be awesome", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Not really.  We kind of went swimming and I forgot to do it", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Did you finish all of your homework at Kims house after school", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Lucy, what have we talked about?  You have to do your homework firs", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Not really.  We kind of went swimming and I forgot to do it", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Im sorry, I just forgot", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Lucy, what have we talked about?  You have to do your homework firs", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Youll have to work on it until 8:00 and then its time for bed, OK?  No T", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Im sorry, I just forgot", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " But, dad", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Youll have to work on it until 8:00 and then its time for bed, OK?  No T", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Homework is important, Lucy.  You have to do it", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 85, "question": " But, dad", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Fine", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Homework is important, Lucy.  You have to do it", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Marcia, this mac and cheese is delicious", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Fine", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Im glad you like it.  I made it from scratch", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Marcia, this mac and cheese is delicious", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Its great.  Why dont you go relax and Ill clean up and help Lucy with he", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Im glad you like it.  I made it from scratch", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Thank you.  I will", "docId": "11-05", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Its great.  Why dont you go relax and Ill clean up and help Lucy with he", "qSentId": 92}]
